folks are having this like revelation like oh the politicians didn't care about the images of
the kids in palestine because they were graping kids and their pdfs they didn't care about the
kids in sandy hook and in all of the schools in the united states where they are shooting them up
they don't care about kids because they don't care about people
i need y'all to understand this these people are sociopathic psychopaths they don't care about
people y'all over here still thinking that politicians are going into politics because
they want to be public servants i'm not saying there aren't a some of you but that's not what
the field is engineered towards the same way that people who go into policing for the most part
go in it for the pension or for applying punishment they're not in there to protect and serve
quit believing the lie that these systems and this infrastructure is set up to protect you
it's just that's the lie and yes we believed it for a minute
now it's time to stop believing it so we can get busy
How black am I going to have to get?